{
    "id": "9f837996f57742db8fe4f13ba6af4b75",
    "title": "Fill In the Blanks",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James .................................. at the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enjoyed himself",
                "enjoyed",
                "enjoyed himselves"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f4aacf60046b4fca900f17e09734ee3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is going to be more difficult .................................. we thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "beeb909c5bef42858d581b401a416d0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not always obstinate, but .................................. she is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sometimes",
                "some time",
                "some times"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "07bbf8954dca40d587e3feed24846f62"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... of money has been wasted on the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "A lot",
                "Lot",
                "Lots"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9ecfddad66bf49a3a746aa35aa7a43f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "How about ......................................... to the theater tonight?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "we go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2b2c05c581c640a08a5768f754b382c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was careless .............................. him to leave the keys of the safe on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6abc532704d42278f8dc384ae33bd3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "How clever ..................................... you to solve the problem so quickly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc6f98f236674882870d7b45902377e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The more he reads ...................................... he understands.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "the less",
                "the lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1fd0e081d7774f4eb81b46e616d83a47"
        },
        {
            "question": "The older we grow ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "we become the wiser",
                "we become wiser",
                "the wiser we become"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0af697d8720d48a4bc05496897d998c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very good ................................... languages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with learning",
                "at learning",
                "at learn"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7ac13962e9c4395ab73bc0415f91468"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is interested ................................. the supernatural.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e78ee8f84404635b9265578654d5ef3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must get my watch ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repair",
                "repaired",
                "repairing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fd0dc874e124ba6b17292125aadecbb"
        }
    ]
}